export default {
  id: 'jplt_word_n5_josusa_1',
  name: 'JPLT N5 조수사',
  data: [
    { question: 'いくつ', answer: ['', '몇 개'] },
    { question: '一つ', answer: ['ひとつ', '1개'] },
    { question: '二つ', answer: ['ふたつ', '2개'] },
    { question: '三つ', answer: ['みっつ', '3개'] },
    { question: '四つ', answer: ['よっつ', '4개'] },
    { question: '五つ', answer: ['いつつ', '5개'] },
    { question: '六つ', answer: ['むっつ', '6개'] },
    { question: '七つ', answer: ['ななつ', '7개'] },
    { question: '八つ', answer: ['やっつ', '8개'] },
    { question: '九つ', answer: ['ここのつ', '9개'] },
    { question: '十', answer: ['とお', '10개'] },
    { question: '何個', answer: ['なんこ', '몇 개 (작은 사물)'] },
    { question: '一個', answer: ['いっこ', '1개'] },
    { question: '二個', answer: ['にこ', '2개'] },
    { question: '三個', answer: ['さんこ', '3개'] },
    { question: '四個', answer: ['よんこ', '4개'] },
    { question: '五個', answer: ['ごこ', '5개'] },
    { question: '六個', answer: ['ろっこ', '6개'] },
    { question: '七個', answer: ['ななこ', '7개'] },
    { question: '八個', answer: ['はっこ', '8개'] },
    { question: '九個', answer: ['きゅうこ', '9개'] },
    { question: '十個', answer: ['じゅっこ · じっこ', '10개'] },
    { question: '何階', answer: ['なんかい · なんがい', '몇 층'] },
    { question: '一階', answer: ['いっかい', '1층'] },
    { question: '二階', answer: ['にかい', '2층'] },
    { question: '三階', answer: ['さんかい · さんがい', '3층'] },
    { question: '四階', answer: ['よんかい', '4층'] },
    { question: '五階', answer: ['ごかい', '5층'] },
    { question: '六階', answer: ['ろっかい', '6층'] },
    { question: '七階', answer: ['ななかい', '7층'] },
    { question: '八階', answer: ['はっかい · はちかい', '8층'] },
    { question: '九階', answer: ['きゅうかい', '9층'] },
    { question: '十階', answer: ['じゅっかい · じっかい', '10층'] },
    { question: '何回', answer: ['なんかい', '몇 회, 몇 번 (횟수)'] },
    { question: '一回', answer: ['いっかい', '1회'] },
    { question: '二回', answer: ['にかい', '2회'] },
    { question: '三回', answer: ['さんかい', '3회'] },
    { question: '四回', answer: ['よんかい', '4회'] },
    { question: '五回', answer: ['ごかい', '5회'] },
    { question: '六回', answer: ['ろっかい', '6회'] },
    { question: '七回', answer: ['ななかい', '7회'] },
    { question: '八回', answer: ['はっかい', '8회'] },
    { question: '九回', answer: ['きゅうかい', '9회'] },
    { question: '十回', answer: ['じゅっかい · じっかい', '10회'] },
    { question: '何番', answer: ['なんばん', '몇 번 (번호)'] },
    { question: '一番', answer: ['いちばん', '1번'] },
    { question: '二番', answer: ['にばん', '2번'] },
    { question: '三番', answer: ['さんばん', '3번'] },
    { question: '四番', answer: ['よんばん', '4번'] },
    { question: '五番', answer: ['ごばん', '5번'] },
    { question: '六番', answer: ['ろくばん', '6번'] },
    { question: '七番', answer: ['ななばん', '7번'] },
    { question: '八番', answer: ['はちばん', '8번'] },
    { question: '九番', answer: ['きゅうばん', '9번'] },
    { question: '十番', answer: ['じゅうばん', '10번'] },
    { question: 'いくら', answer: ['', '얼마'] },
    { question: '一円', answer: ['いちえん', '1엔'] },
    { question: '二円', answer: ['にえん', '2엔'] },
    { question: '三円', answer: ['さんえん', '3엔'] },
    { question: '四円', answer: ['よえん', '4엔'] },
    { question: '五円', answer: ['ごえん', '5엔'] },
    { question: '六円', answer: ['ろくえん', '6엔'] },
    { question: '七円', answer: ['ななえん', '7엔'] },
    { question: '八円', answer: ['はちえん', '8엔'] },
    { question: '九円', answer: ['きゅうえん', '9엔'] },
    { question: '十円', answer: ['じゅうえん', '10엔'] },
    { question: '何年', answer: ['なんねん', '몇 년'] },
    { question: '一年', answer: ['いちねん', '1년'] },
    { question: '二年', answer: ['にねん', '2년'] },
    { question: '三年', answer: ['さんねん', '3년'] },
    { question: '四年', answer: ['よねん', '4년'] },
    { question: '五年', answer: ['ごねん', '5년'] },
    { question: '六年', answer: ['ろくねん', '6년'] },
    { question: '七年', answer: ['ななねん · しちねん', '7년'] },
    { question: '八年', answer: ['はちねん', '8년'] },
    { question: '九年', answer: ['きゅうねん', '9년'] },
    { question: '十年', answer: ['じゅうねん', '10년'] },
    { question: '何月', answer: ['なんがつ', '몇 월'] },
    { question: '一月', answer: ['いちがつ', '1월'] },
    { question: '二月', answer: ['にがつ', '2월'] },
    { question: '三月', answer: ['さんがつ', '3월'] },
    { question: '四月', answer: ['しがつ', '4월'] },
    { question: '五月', answer: ['ごがつ', '5월'] },
    { question: '六月', answer: ['ろくがつ', '6월'] },
    { question: '七月', answer: ['しちがつ', '7월'] },
    { question: '八月', answer: ['はちがつ', '8월'] },
    { question: '九月', answer: ['くがつ', '9월'] },
    { question: '十月', answer: ['じゅうがつ', '10월'] },
    { question: '十一月', answer: ['じゅういちがつ', '11월'] },
    { question: '十二月', answer: ['じゅうにがつ', '12월'] },
    { question: '何日', answer: ['なんにち', '며칠'] },
    { question: '一日', answer: ['ついたち', '1일'] },
    { question: '二日', answer: ['ふつか', '2일'] },
    { question: '三日', answer: ['みっか', '3일'] },
    { question: '四日', answer: ['よっか', '4일'] },
    { question: '五日', answer: ['いつか', '5일'] },
    { question: '六日', answer: ['むいか', '6일'] },
    { question: '七日', answer: ['なのか', '7일'] },
    { question: '八日', answer: ['ようか', '8일'] },
    { question: '九日', answer: ['ここのか', '9일'] },
    { question: '十日', answer: ['とおか', '10일'] },
    { question: '十一日', answer: ['じゅういちにち', '11일'] },
    { question: '十二日', answer: ['じゅうににち', '12일'] },
    { question: '十三日', answer: ['じゅうさんにち', '13일'] },
    { question: '十四日', answer: ['じゅうよっか', '14일'] },
    { question: '十五日', answer: ['じゅうごにち', '15일'] },
    { question: '十六日', answer: ['じゅうろくにち', '16일'] },
    { question: '十七日', answer: ['じゅうしちにち', '17일'] },
    { question: '十八日', answer: ['じゅうはちにち', '18일'] },
    { question: '十九日', answer: ['じゅうくにち', '19일'] },
    { question: '二十日', answer: ['はつか', '20일'] },
    { question: '二十一日', answer: ['にじゅういちにち', '21일'] },
    { question: '二十二日', answer: ['にじゅうににち', '22일'] },
    { question: '二十三日', answer: ['にじゅうさんにち', '23일'] },
    { question: '二十四日', answer: ['にじゅうよっか', '24일'] },
    { question: '二十五日', answer: ['にじゅうごにち', '25일'] },
    { question: '二十六日', answer: ['にじゅうろくにち', '26일'] },
    { question: '二十七日', answer: ['にじゅうしちにち', '27일'] },
    { question: '二十八日', answer: ['にじゅうはちにち', '28일'] },
    { question: '二十九日', answer: ['にじゅうくにち', '29일'] },
    { question: '三十日', answer: ['さんじゅうにち', '30일'] },
    { question: '三十一日', answer: ['さんじゅういちにち', '31일'] },
    { question: '何時', answer: ['なんじ', '몇 시'] },
    { question: '一時', answer: ['いちじ', '1시'] },
    { question: '二時', answer: ['にじ', '2시'] },
    { question: '三時', answer: ['さんじ', '3시'] },
    { question: '四時', answer: ['よじ', '4시'] },
    { question: '五時', answer: ['ごじ', '5시'] },
    { question: '六時', answer: ['ろくじ', '6시'] },
    { question: '七時', answer: ['しちじ', '7시'] },
    { question: '八時', answer: ['はちじ', '8시'] },
    { question: '九時', answer: ['くじ', '9시'] },
    { question: '十時', answer: ['じゅうじ', '10시'] },
    { question: '十一時', answer: ['じゅういちじ', '11시'] },
    { question: '十二時', answer: ['じゅうにじ', '12시'] },
    { question: '何分', answer: ['なんぷん', '몇 분'] },
    { question: '一分', answer: ['いっぷん', '1분'] },
    { question: '二分', answer: ['にふん', '2분'] },
    { question: '三分', answer: ['さんぷん', '3분'] },
    { question: '四分', answer: ['よんぷん', '4분'] },
    { question: '五分', answer: ['ごふん', '5분'] },
    { question: '六分', answer: ['ろっぷん', '6분'] },
    { question: '七分', answer: ['ななふん · しちふん', '7분'] },
    { question: '八分', answer: ['はっぷん · はちふん', '8분'] },
    { question: '九分', answer: ['きゅうふん', '9분'] },
    { question: '十分', answer: ['じゅっぷん · じっぷん', '10분'] },
    { question: '何曜日', answer: ['なんようび', '무슨 요일'] },
    { question: '日曜日', answer: ['にちようび', '일요일'] },
    { question: '月曜日', answer: ['げつようび', '월요일'] },
    { question: '火曜日', answer: ['かようび', '화요일'] },
    { question: '水曜日', answer: ['すいようび', '수요일'] },
    { question: '木曜日', answer: ['もくようび', '목요일'] },
    { question: '金曜日', answer: ['きんようび', '금요일'] },
    { question: '土曜日', answer: ['どようび', '토요일'] },
    { question: '何杯', answer: ['なんばい', '몇 잔, 몇 공기'] },
    { question: '一杯', answer: ['いっぱい', '1잔'] },
    { question: '二杯', answer: ['にはい', '2잔'] },
    { question: '三杯', answer: ['さんばい', '3잔'] },
    { question: '四杯', answer: ['よんはい', '4잔'] },
    { question: '五杯', answer: ['ごはい', '5잔'] },
    { question: '六杯', answer: ['ろっぱい', '6잔'] },
    { question: '七杯', answer: ['ななはい', '7잔'] },
    { question: '八杯', answer: ['はっぱい', '8잔'] },
    { question: '九杯', answer: ['きゅうはい', '9잔'] },
    { question: '十杯', answer: ['じゅっぱい · じっぱい', '10잔'] },
    { question: '何倍', answer: ['なんばい', '몇 배'] },
    { question: '一倍', answer: ['いちばい', '1배'] },
    { question: '二倍', answer: ['にばい', '2배'] },
    { question: '三杯', answer: ['さんばい', '3배'] },
    { question: '四倍', answer: ['よんばい', '4배'] },
    { question: '五倍', answer: ['ごばい', '5배'] },
    { question: '六倍', answer: ['ろくばい', '6배'] },
    { question: '七倍', answer: ['ななばい', '7배'] },
    { question: '八倍', answer: ['はちばい', '8배'] },
    { question: '九倍', answer: ['きゅうばい', '9배'] },
    { question: '十倍', answer: ['じゅうばい', '10배'] },
    { question: '何本', answer: ['なんぼん', '몇 자루, 몇 병 (가늘고 긴 것)'] },
    { question: '一本', answer: ['いっぽん', '1병'] },
    { question: '二本', answer: ['にほん', '2병'] },
    { question: '三本', answer: ['さんぼん', '3병'] },
    { question: '四本', answer: ['よんほん', '4병'] },
    { question: '五本', answer: ['ごほん', '5병'] },
    { question: '六本', answer: ['ろっぽん', '6병'] },
    { question: '七本', answer: ['ななほん', '7병'] },
    { question: '八本', answer: ['はっぽん', '8병'] },
    { question: '九本', answer: ['きゅうほん', '9병'] },
    { question: '十本', answer: ['じゅっぽん · じっぽん', '10병'] },
    { question: '何枚', answer: ['なんまい', '몇 매, 몇 장 (얇고 평평한 것)'] },
    { question: '一枚', answer: ['いちまい', '1장'] },
    { question: '二枚', answer: ['にまい', '2장'] },
    { question: '三枚', answer: ['さんまい', '3장'] },
    { question: '四枚', answer: ['よんまい', '4장'] },
    { question: '五枚', answer: ['ごまい', '5장'] },
    { question: '六枚', answer: ['ろくまい', '6장'] },
    { question: '七枚', answer: ['しちまい · ななまい', '7장'] },
    { question: '八枚', answer: ['はちまい', '8장'] },
    { question: '九枚', answer: ['きゅうまい', '9장'] },
    { question: '十枚', answer: ['じゅうまい', '10장'] },
    { question: '何人', answer: ['なんにん', '몇 명'] },
    { question: '一人', answer: ['ひとり', '1명'] },
    { question: '二人', answer: ['ふたり', '2명'] },
    { question: '三人', answer: ['さんにん', '3명'] },
    { question: '四人', answer: ['よにん', '4명'] },
    { question: '五人', answer: ['ごにん', '5명'] },
    { question: '六人', answer: ['ろくにん', '6명'] },
    { question: '七人', answer: ['しちにん · ななにん', '7명'] },
    { question: '八人', answer: ['はちにん', '8명'] },
    { question: '九人', answer: ['きゅうにん · くにん', '9명'] },
    { question: '十人', answer: ['じゅうにん', '10명'] },
    { question: '何匹', answer: ['なんびき', '몇 마리 (작은 동물)'] },
    { question: '一匹', answer: ['いっぴき', '1마리'] },
    { question: '二匹', answer: ['にひき', '2마리'] },
    { question: '三匹', answer: ['さんびき', '3마리'] },
    { question: '四匹', answer: ['よんひき', '4마리'] },
    { question: '五匹', answer: ['ごひき', '5마리'] },
    { question: '六匹', answer: ['ろっぴき', '6마리'] },
    { question: '七匹', answer: ['ななひき', '7마리'] },
    { question: '八匹', answer: ['はっぴき', '8마리'] },
    { question: '九匹', answer: ['きゅうひき', '9마리'] },
    { question: '十匹', answer: ['じゅっぴき · じっぴき', '10마리'] }
  ]
}
